■ gullandrea693@gmail.com | 🛠 handgull.netlify.app | 🖸 github.com/handgull | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/handgull



Milano(MI), Italy

Presentation

My name is Andrea, I am born in 1996 and I have successfully developed the good habit of continuous learning, thanks to the book "Atomic Habits". I enjoy creating and designing useful things with a simple UI.

I don't like using outdated tools or working in environments where the architecture is not valued (since the paycheck will come later).

Check my personal side project app: **ZYME** available on android and iOS! It's a calories counter, i hope you will like it!

Skills (In order of proficiency) _

I consider myself mainly a frontend developer, but I also have experience as a full-stack. I have already worked with microservices and microfrontends too! Lately i am playing with gen AI (LLMs, RAGs, NLP...)

Frontend Angular (Reactive programming lover), Flutter (Bloc and Provider for the DI), React (Redux / Jotai / Zustand as state managers).

Backend Node.js (Nest.js, Fastify as main choices), PostgreSQL (usually with PrismaORM or DrizzleORM), LangChain (novice level).

Infrastructure Git (usually with CI), Docker, RabbitMQ, Kubernetes, Linux, Terraform, Firebase / Supabase.

Soft Skills Agile method, Ability to provide precise estimates, Teamwork, Adaptability, Empathy, Pair programming.

Education

ITIS (Giacomo Fauser) Novara(NO), Italy High school diploma, computer science Set. 2010 - Aug. 2015

Bachelor degree, computer science

• LEFT STUDIES at my 3rd year, with 4 exams left. I noticed that I couldn't study and work since I was already studying for work.

Work Experience (5+ yrs)_

Freelancer Comignago(NO), Italia Feb 2022 - NOW

Mobile/Web Developer

- Working with Angular since 2018.
- Working with Flutter since 2020.
- Working with Node.js since 2018.

Ennova research Lomazzo(CO), Italia May 2021 - Feb 2022

Software Engineer

- We worked in big teams, divided in sub-teams according to the **AGILE** method
- Worked in big projects for clients like FAAC, Leroy Merlin, Eni etc...
- Technical Skills: Angular, React, Flutter.

SOFTECH Gallarate(VA), Italia Junior developer Sep 2018 - Feb 2020

- SOFTECH offers systems, software and complete services in the field of monitoring and supervision of human interactions with the environment
- Developing external commissions as a full-stack novice.
- · Making implementation choices and constantly looking for news/technologies that could benefit the company
- Developing frontend of one of my company's biggest projects (airport industry)
- Technical Skills: Angular, Node. is, Leaflet and GIS Databases.

Secondary interests _

I love to study **nutrition** and **working out**! Proud owner of a **pet hedgehog** named Kenny. 🤏

Languages_

English Good reader, troubles forming complex sentences during a heavily technical conversation, but I make myself understood. Italiano Native proficiency.

Thankfully generative AI is a really promising helper in this field, i can self host a SLM (so there are no privacy issues) to provide real time translations and more!